Abdul Hamid Hasibuan

Frontend Developer

Yogyakarta, Indonesia, 085330158423, abdulhamid.dev@gmail.com

PROFILE

A tech enthusiast who has studied the programming profession. Started working on projects since 2017 which are website-based and have mastered several stacks until now. Likes to explore technology and dares to trial and error something that has not been tried, especially programming languages

EXPERIENCE

Jul 2019 - Present

IT Staff, PT PELANGI INDODATA, Bekasi

- 1. Maintenance of reconciliation programs (such as creating new reconciliation programs or adjusting existing programs)
- 2. Maintenance of warehouse databases (such as backup and restore)
- 3. Frontend development (maintenance of existing applications and creation of mobile applications or websites on the frontend as needed)

Jul 2017 - Jun 2019

Web Developer, ZADA KREATIF MEDIA, Yogyakarta

- 1. Design business flow applications required by clients
- 2. Create application designs such as database designs, UI/UX, etc
- 3. Development of web applications according to design

EDUCATION

Sep 2015 – Sep 2019 (Bachelor)

Informatics Engineering, STMIK AKAKOM YOGYAKARTA, Yogyakarta Graduated with high honor, 3.74 / 4

LANGUAGES	Indonesia	Native Speaker	English Good working knowledge	
	React Native	Experienced	Typescript	Experienced
	Next.js	Experienced	Codeigniter	Experienced
SKILLS	React.js	Experienced	Javascript	Experienced
-				